## **NOAH SHAW**

#### **SUMMARY**

Software Engineering student with experience in Java, Python, and C++. Possesses strong writing and oral communication skills, is passionate about analytical problem solving and life-long learning, and has years of experience working in collaborative, project-oriented teams. Experience with data structures, algorithms, object-oriented programming, and scripting languages.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science: Software Engineering (minor: Communication) Expected May 2024; GPA: 3.932

Point Loma Nazarene University, San Diego, CA

### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

#### **New Student Engagement Intern**

August 2023 - May 2024

- Served as an intern under the director of New Student Engagement
- Worked closely with other New Student Engagement interns and the New Student Engagement director to plan two events for the freshman class and two for the Alpha Team
- Oversaw and ran meetings for 60 student volunteers who led Alpha Groups and Family Groups (described below), which included emphases on leadership and personal growth

### **Computer Science Teaching Assistant**

January 2022 – December 2023

- Assisted the professor in teaching classes for both Java and C++, across 4 separate semesters
- Assisted 20 to 30 students per semester with their class assignments, helping reinforce good coding practices and debugging techniques
- Graded class assignments under criteria of code functionality and quality

#### **Service Learning Project**

September 2023 –December 2023

- Collaborated in a team to provide value for the Adult Degree Completion Program and Graduate Program of the University
- Utilized Excel to analyse raw survey data from student satisfaction reports and develop two 100+ page reports to provide the University

#### **Family Group Leader**

August 2022 – December 2022

- Co-led a family group of 7 "Alpha Leaders" on a weekly basis, with the goal of mentoring them as they lead their own Alpha Group
- Collaborated on and executed events with the Family Group team for the freshman class and Alpha leaders, as well as planned events for my own family group

#### Alpha Leader

August 2021 – May 2022

- Served a dorm hall of 30 freshman by co-leading 30 "Alpha Group" meetings on Monday nights, a
  dorm-based small group for freshman with the goal of getting them connected to their hall and
  acclimated to university life
- Helped coordinate and run multiple events for the freshman class

#### RELEVANT COURSEWORK

Objects and Elementary Data Structures, Data Structures and Algorithms, Operating Systems,
 Software Engineering, Computer Architecture and Assembly Language, Software Project, Project
 Management and Quality Assurance, Unix And Python Scripting for Computational Science,
 Networking & Security, Data Base Systems and Web Integration, Network+ Exam Preparation,
 Programming Languages

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Languages Java, Python, C++, C#
- Basic experience with the Google Suite and Microsoft Office Suite

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Developed strong written communication and presentation skills through writing and selfpublishing two books through Amazon KDP: Fan or Follower: The Gospel Message and What We Do About It, and Shipwreck: The Modern Church and Its Path Toward Disaster
- Studying to receive the CompTIA Network+ Certification April 2024
- Served as Vice President of my University's Concert Band
- Volunteered six years for Royal Family Kids Camp, a non-profit summer camp for foster children ages six to twelve